That's right, sadness is kindness,
Selfishness is strength, It's okay to be
lost, Just start walking, One more time!
I always answer to someone's expectations,
I like being praised, A little pause.
.. and we are back.
A little pause...
and we are back.
I commend all those
who have advanced to the
finals for the third level
of the tuning exams.
Well, there's one person missing,
but still, congratulations.
Sensei?
Hmm?
I have a question for you.
About Sasuke?
I'm sorry.
I don't know much about that, I'm afraid.
But I wouldn't worry too much.
From here on, it's up to you, Sasuke.
Sakura, I have to leave, so I'm counting
on you to get the details about the finals.
Huh?
Oh, okay.
Here, including the absent Sasuke,
we have five ninja from the Leaf Village.
Three from the Sand Village.
And one from the Sound Village.
And now... Now I will begin the
explanation of the final rounds.
Well, it's about time!
The preliminaries are done.
They're moving on to the final rounds.
While all these countries are busy racing
to expand their military might,
the birds are still singing.
I believe that this country of ours has
been at peace for far, far too long.
Then let me do it.
Hmm... I don't know.
How much fun would it be to take out an
old man like the Hokage anyway?
What's the problem?
You're not still having second thoughts
about it, are you, Orochimaru?
From now on, each of the
Hidden Villages will clash
with each other in a
long and violent struggle.
Even the Sound Village won't escape that
violence.
And it's your intention.
Your intention?
To be the trigger for all that hostility?
By using Sasuke as a bullet?
...Isn't that correct?
Hm... You guess very well... So well that
it's a bit creepy, in fact.
The curse mark that was given to him
appears to have been sealed by Kakashi.
But in any event, that is not my concern.
While there is still some darkness left in
his heart, we must act.
And that's why I want you to abduct him!
Hold it!
It's unusual.
It's unusual for you to act so hastily,
is it not?
Perhaps, but there's still a little
something that's troubling me.
Is it Naruto Uzumaki?
You're quite sharp, aren't you,
Kabuto?
According to your
information, contact with that
nine-tailed one has altered
Sasuke's heart and mind.
So much so that Naruto now holds a certain
influence over our Sasuke.
The thing to do is to get Sasuke away from
him immediately.
Then it will be so easy to make him mine
forever.
Very well.
Hmm... that face... I wonder what's going
on in his head.
In the final rounds, each of you will put
your battle skills on display.
You'll demonstrate the
power and control that
you've achieved in your
respective disciplines.
Accordingly, the final battles will
commence one month from now.
Wait, we're not gonna do it right here and
now?
This is to provide a suitable period of
preparation.
What do you mean by that?
Simply this.
In addition to announcing the conclusion
of the preliminary matches to each
country's leaders, we must
also have some time to prepare
and distribute the summons
for the final selection.
Not to mention that you
examinees are going to need
time to prepare for
something that is this important.
This old man sure likes to beat around the
bush.
Look, I don't really get what you're
trying to say.
What's the point of this?
I mean that to know your adversaries and
prepare yourselves, you need time.
Even though up to this point all the
battles have been real battles,
as I'm sure you can all
attest, they were conducted on
the premise that you were
fighting an unknown enemy.
But that's no longer the case now that
you've battled each other.
Yeah, seriously.
I would never have dreamed that this guy
could turn sand into a weapon.
So in order to make the finals fair and
just, we're giving you this month,
each of you must embrace the opportunity
to practice hard and learn some new tricks.
Because by now everyone here
knows your techniques, so using
your old tired tricks is a
sure way to lose in the finals.
And remember to get some rest as well.
This isn't some vacation!
I won't have any time to relax!
I've got to train harder than ever!
I suppose brilliance can sometimes have
its disadvantages.
We failed to avoid
Orochimaru's watchful eye,
and it's most
unfortunate for both of us.
Orochimaru's watchful eye, and it's most
He's so young, but
the seeds of evil have
already taken root just
waiting to be exploited.
He'll be ripe for Orochimaru's special
ninjutsu.
Well, well, Kakashi.
Foiling my attack by striking from my
blind spot, huh?
But now, are you ready to take me on?
Next time you should station at least ten
guards.